// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of these is a tropical rain forest?",
    answer: "Sinharajaya",
    options: [
      "wilpattuwa",
      "Sinharajaya",
      "Yala",
      "Kanneliya forest"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who was the king who initiate the construction Ruwanwelisaya?",
    answer: "King Dutugamunu",
    options: [
      "King Mahasen",
      "King kashyapa",
      "King Dutugamunu",
      "King Mahasen"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Pasikuda beach is located in which district?",
    answer: "Baticaloa District",
    options: [
      "Baticaloa District",
      "Ampara District",
      "Trincomalee District",
      "Puttalama District"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the largest forest in sri lanaka?",
    answer: "Wilpattuwa",
    options: [
      "Wilpattuwa",
      "Sinharajaya",
      "Yala",
      "Kanneliya forest"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Where is Dunhinda waterfalls located?",
    answer: "Badulla",
    options: [
      "Kandy",
      "Nuwara-eliya",
      "Rathnapura",
      "Badulla"
    ]
  },
 
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who was the king who reigned in sigiriya?",
    answer: "King Kashyapa",
    options: [
      "Kind Dutugamunu",
      "King Kashyapa",
      "King Dewanampiyathissa",
      "King Pandukabaya"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the highest waterfall in Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Bambarakanda Waterfall",
    options: [
      "Diyaluma Waterfall",
      "Rawana Ella",
      "Bambarakanda Waterfall",
      "Dunhinda Waterfall"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "who was the founding ruler of Polonnaruwa Kingdom?",
    answer: "King Vijayabahu",
    options: [
      "Kind Parakcramabahu",
      "King Nishshankamalla",
      "King Vijayabahu",
      "King Pandukabaya"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "In which district is a natural harbor located in sri lanka?",
    answer: "Trincomalee District",
    options: [
      "Jaffna District",
      "Galle District",
      "Colombo District",
      "Trincomalee District"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of these is located in kandy district?",
    answer: "Place of the Tooth",
    options: [
      "Place of the Tooth",
      "Ruwanwelisaya",
      "Nine-Arch Bridge",
      "Lotus Tower"
    ]
  },
];